4myrebate.com 2014-09-25

# Rebate Privacy Statement

###  General Information 

Our website security is unmatched anywhere on the Internet. Once you type your information, it is sent instantly, directly to our order processing system, which is on a server separate from the internet. This is done to protect you from unauthorized use of the information you are sending to our server. 

###  Contact Information 

Our postal address is: 

Rebate Center   
PO Box 1339   
Deerfield Beach, FL 33442 

You can e-mail us at customerservice@help.4myrebate.com or reach us by phone at 1-800-286-9146. 

Rebate Center has developed relationships with our customers based on respect and integrity. We're aware of the of the trust and confidence you demonstrate when you visit our website and provide us with information. The Privacy Notice below is posted to demonstrate our adherence to the practices you'll find common to the best websites online. We promise that we will treat your information with the same honesty and sensitivity that we have displayed throughout our company's history. 

We will never share your email address , phone number, personal or company information with any unrelated 3rd party except as necessary to fulfill transactions that you initiate. 

If you have any questions or concerns about our Privacy Notice, please call us toll-free at 1-800-286-9146 or e-mail us at customerservice@help.4myrebate.com or send a letter to the above address. 

### Rebate Center Privacy Notice

By visiting the Rebate Center’s website you agree to accept the practices described in this Privacy Notice. 

Changes to this Privacy Notice, Conditions of Use and Notices:: 

This Privacy Notice and our Terms of Use will change over time and the use of information which we gather now is subject to these Notices and Terms as modified. Please check this page periodically as you continue to use our site to see if any changes have been made. This privacy notice was most recently changed on October 1, 2008. If you visit our Web site your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Legal Notices, including the application of the laws of the State of Florida. 

### Children

Rebate Center does not offer rebates to persons under the age of 18. If you are under the age of 18, you cannot conduct business on this site. 

### Personal Information Collected By Rebate Center:

The Rebate Center uses information that we collect from our visitors to personalize and improve your visit at the Rebate Center. We gather the following types of information: 

### Information you give us: 

The Rebate Center collects any information which you enter on our website. This information is normally provided when you search, buy, participate in a contest, sweepstakes or on-line survey, or when you communicate with any of our departments such as customer service, sales or technical services through our website, telephone, mail or fax. You also provide information when you establish an account with us. Examples of the type of information you may supply us with include your name, address, telephone number and e-mail addresses. 

### Automatic Information collected by us:

We (or agents on our behalf) collect anonymous information from visits to our sites through the use of "Web Beacons." Web Beacons are simply web page elements which may employ cookie technology that enable us to record anonymous data about visits to or transactions made on our web site. This anonymous information is sometimes known as "clickstream data." We may use this data to analyze trends and statistics to improve your online experience, or customer service. No personal data is collected through the use of Web Beacons on our sites. Through the use of cookies, we may also collect and analyze the IP address used to connect your computer to the Internet; computer and connection information such as your browser type and version; operating system and platform; purchase history; confirmation when you open e-mail that we send you; and the URLs which lead you to and around our Web site including the date and time. Your browser allows you to reject cookies and software is available from third parties which will allow you to visit our Web site without providing this information. You are welcomed at our Web site if you use this software but we will not be able to offer you our personalized services and we will be unable to accept any orders from you. 

### Sharing of Information with third-parties:

### Merchandizing Partners:

Rebate Center works with Merchandizing Partners to offer consumers rebate choices such as selected merchandise or services instead of the customary cash rebate. For those customers who elect to redeem their rebate by selecting the merchandise or services offered by our Merchandizing Partners, we provide the Merchandizing Partners with the customer's information necessary for them to fulfill the customer's selection. Such information will include the name, address, phone, and email address of the customer. Use of customers' information by Merchandizing Partners is governed by the privacy policy of the company offering the particular merchandize or product.

### Independent Contractors:

We may employ other companies or individuals to provide certain services to us such as analyzing customer lists and data, providing marketing assistance, or consulting services. These third parties will have access to the information needed to perform their functions but cannot use that information for any other purpose. Any 3rd parties who use our data will be fully bound by this privacy policy. In no event will the data being used by any unrelated third party include your email address.

### Aggregate information:

From time to time we may provide aggregate customer information (e.g.: rebate dollar value, category of product from rebate, job function, industry) by Rebate Center during the processing of rebates. The recipients of this aggregate information may be 3rd parties, vendors and affiliated business partners. This information does not allow 3rd parties, vendors and affiliated business partners to identify you individually in any way. 

### Third Party Transaction-Level Data:

If you visit our site from a third-party site the third-party site may be able to access select information from your individual transaction information. In order to track and credit your transaction the third-party site may give you a unique code, cookie or graphic which will uniquely identify you. This will only happen if you link directly from a third party site to our Web site. Any transactions made at our Web site while such a code is active will be reported back to the third party site. We will only report non-personal information to these sites such as the date of the transaction, the product(s) purchased and the amount spent. We will not report any information to these third party sites that will allow them to personally identify you and will never share your email address with any 3rd party. The presence of a 3rd party navigation bar atop our site is an indication that the third party site may be able to see your activity on our site. 

### Link to Third Party Site:

Our Web site contains certain links to third party sites, such as our vendors. Rebate Center is not responsible or liable for the privacy practices or content found on these sites. We suggest that you check the Privacy Notice of each site you visit. 

### Law Enforcement and Protection of Users:

We will release personally identifiable information to third parties and organizations when we believe it is appropriate for us to do so to comply with the law. We will also do so to cooperate with law enforcement investigations, comply with court orders or subpoenas, protect the legal rights of us and our users, or when we believe it is needed for fraud protection and/ or credit risk reduction. 

### Business Transfer:

In the unlikely event that Rebate Center is sold, has its assets acquired or transferred, whether voluntarily or involuntarily, or merges or becomes affiliated with any other division, individual or entity, any customer information owned or under the control of Rebate Center may be one of the transferred assets. 

### Security:

We employ the latest 128-bit encryption technology in all areas of the site which require you to provide your personal or account information, including online ordering, order status, catalog request and most contest forms. Your name, your personal information and especially your credit card number are safely stored in our proprietary systems behind our firewall. Once you type your personal information, it is sent instantly, encrypted, directly to our order processing system which is on a server separate from our internet server. To make sure you have the latest security features on your browser, you may want to download the most recent version of your favorite browser, which should have full SSL support.
